export const triviaQuestions = [
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "1",
        question: "How many countries start with the letter V?",
        answer: "None"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "2",
        question: "What animal's English name matches its scientific name?",
        answer: "The Chimpanzee (Pan Troglodytes)"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "3",
        question: "If I were to put a diamond in a cup and place it upside down on a table, then later take my cup and put it in the fridge, where is the diamond now?",
        answer: "Still in the cup"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "4",
        question: "What is 10 + 20?",
        answer: "25"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "5",
        question:"Which is heavier, a pound of feathers or a pound of bricks?",
        answer:"A pound of bricks, because bricks are heavier than feathers"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "6",
        question:"Interestingly, Dolphins are mammals, what other sea creature is also a mammal?",
        answer:"A Sailfish"
    },
    {
        round: "AI is going to take all our jobs",
        number: "7",
        question:"Mike's Mum has 4 kids, April, May, June, and who?",
        answer:"It's impossible to tell, the question is ambiguous"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "1",
        question:"Three examples of figurative language are Onomatopoeia, Synatx, and Hyperbole.",
        answer:"Synatx is not a type of figurative language (Bonus points: Other examples include Metaphor, Simile, Aliteration, Idiom and Personification)"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "2",
        question:"An example of a Metaphor is 'The party was like a scene from a film'.",
        answer:"That's an example of a Simile, not a Metaphor (Bonus points: A Metaphor would be 'The party was a scene from a film')"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "3",
        question:"Personification is when a word is used to imitate a sound, like 'buzz' or 'whisper'.",
        answer:"buzz' and 'whisper' are instances of onomatopoeia (Bonus points: Personification would be 'The wind whispered through the trees'.)"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "4",
        question:"Humans have 48 chromosomes in every cell of their body.",
        answer:"That is too many chromosomes (Bonus points: Correct number is 46)"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "5",
        question:"Identical twins occur when two separate eggs are fertilized by two different sperm at the same time.",
        answer:"This is an example of a fraternal twin (Bonus points: Identical twins occur when a single fertilized egg splits into two embryos)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "6",
        question:"Blood type is determined by a single gene with two alleles",
        answer:"It has three alleles (Bonus points: They are A, B, and O)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "7",
        question:"In Excel, a 'macro' refers to a type of chart used for data visualization.",
        answer:"A macro is not a chart (Bonus points: It's a recorded sequence of actions to automate tasks)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "8",
        question:"The function '=SUM(A1:A10)' in Excel will multiply the values from A1 to A10.",
        answer:"This function adds, not multiplies (Bonus points: To multiply, use '=PRODUCT(A1:A10)')"
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "9",
        question:"Excel automatically saves all your work every 10 minutes to prevent data loss.",
        answer:"Excel does not autosave by default (Bonus points: Autosave needs to be enabled manually or through settings)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "10",
        question:"Alexander McQueen was an American fashion designer known for his work in haute couture.",
        answer:"He was actually British, not American (Bonus points: He was known for his bold, emotional designs and extravagant runway shows)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "11",
        question:"Alexander McQueen was awarded 'Designer of the Year' at the British Fashion Awards four times before 2000.",
        answer:"He won it four times, but not all before 2000 (Bonus points: He won in 1996, 1997, 2001, and 2003)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "12",
        question:"McQueen has made designs for popular musicians such as David Bowie's iconic Union Jack coat, Lady Gaga's outfit in her music video for 'Bad Romance' and Justin Timberlake for his performance during the 2004 Superbowl.",
        answer:"He hasn't designed for Justin Timberlake (Bonus points: His 2004 Superbowl costume was for Janet Jackson). "
    },{
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "13",
        question:"Drake's debut studio album, titled 'Take Care,' was released in 2010.",
        answer:"His debut album is 'Thank Me Later' (Bonus points: 'Take Care' is his second album)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "14",
        question:"Drake started his career as an actor on the American TV show 'The Wire.",
        answer:"He wasn't on an American TV show' (Bonus points: He appeared in Canadian TV show 'Degrassi: The Next Generation)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "15",
        question:"Drake's full name is Anthony Drake Graham son to Sandi and Dennis Graham.",
        answer:"That is not his full name (Bonus points: His full name is Aubrey Drake Graham)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "16",
        question:"Michael Jackson's debut solo album contained many memorable tracks including 'Ain't No Sunshine', 'Thriller' and 'Rockin Robin'.",
        answer:"'Thriller' was not on his debut album (Bonus points: It's the title track of his sixth studio album)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "17",
        question:"Michael Jackson once tried to purchase Marvel Comics, when they filed for bankruptcy in the 1990's, to become Iron Man, but was rejected by Stan Lee.",
        answer:"He didn't want to be Iron Man (Bonus points: His goal was to be Spiderman)."
    },
    {
        round: "Umm actually",
        number: "18",
        question:"Michael Jackson was previously married to Debbie Marie Presley, daughter of Elvis Presley.",
        answer:"He was married to Lisa Marie Presley (Bonus points: Debbie was the name of his second wife)."
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "1",
        question:"A renowned space agency, inspired by a celestial figure from ancient lore, launches an ambitious project. This endeavor, a sequel to a historic achievement from a bygone era, aims to venture back to a familiar yet distant terrain.",
        answer:"NASA's Artemis Mission"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "2",
        question:"This light-hearted competition, held in a country famous for its natural beauty, sees various contestants vying for the title, each with its own quirky traits and fan following. This is not without controversy as this year the polls where heavily influenced by a large scale international marketing campaign spearheaded up by a popular talk show host.",
        answer:"New Zealand's Bird of the Century Competition"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "3",
        question:"In a curious twist of cinematic fate, two vastly different films find themselves sharing the spotlight in an unexpected cultural mashup. Their simultaneous release sparks a quirky blend of fandoms and discussions, leading to the birth of a new term, a blend of their names.",
        answer:"Barbenheimer"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "4",
        question:"In a revealing and deeply personal memoir, a prince steps out of the shadow of royalty to share his unfiltered life story. This book, capturing headlines and stirring conversations worldwide, delves into his unique upbringing, the tragic loss of his mother, and his struggles.",
        answer:"Prince Harry's Autobiography 'Spare'"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "5",
        question:"A match that became the most-watched television event of the year. The encounter wasn't just a game but a cultural moment, showcasing the rising popularity and significance of a previously unthought of sport on a global stage.",
        answer:"Matildas vs France Soccer Match"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "6",
        question:"In a bold and controversial move, one of the most recognizable social media platforms undergoes a dramatic transformation. Spearheaded by its new owner, the polorising billionaire entrepreneur, the platform shifts from its well-known name and logo, embracing a new identity.",
        answer:"Twitter's Rebrand to X"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "7",
        question:"In a groundbreaking development, a new digital entity emerges, offering a level of interaction and understanding previously unseen. This tool quickly becomes a go-to resource for information, creativity, and learning.",
        answer:"Release of ChatGPT"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "8",
        question:"In a turbulent region steeped in decades of conflict, a militant group, known for its contentious stance against a neighboring nation, initiates a series of aggressive actions. These incidents, involving the use of force, escalate tensions and provoke widespread international concern.",
        answer:"Hamas attacks Israel"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "9",
        question:"A trailblazing private space venture, known for pushing the boundaries of cosmic travel, faced a dramatic setback. This incident, occurring during a crucial trial phase, turned a moment of high expectations into a stark reminder of the perils inherent in conquering the final frontier.",
        answer:"SpaceX's Starship Rocket Explosion"
    },
    {
        round: "Jordan's Sparknotes",
        number: "10",
        question:" In a twist of fate beneath the waves, a vessel designed for deep-sea exploration, named after the deities of primordial strength, confronts the relentless might of the ocean. This craft, built to unveil the secrets of the abyss, succumbs to the very element it sought to conquer.",
        answer:"OceanGate's Titan Submersible Implosion"
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"1A",
        question:"Exotic Culinary Delights",
        answer:"Players describe the most unusual food they've ever eaten"
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"2A",
        question:"Dream Holidays",
        answer:"Players talk about the a holiday they have been on."
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"3A",
        question:"School Excurions",
        answer:"Players describe a memorable school excursion they've been on"
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"1B",
        question:"Unbelievable Personal Experience",
        answer:"Each player tells a story about an incredible or unusual personal experience they've had."
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"2B",
        question:"Bizarre Job Experiences",
        answer:"Players describe the strangest job they've ever had or a peculiar task they had to perform in a job."
    },
    {
        round:"Put your money where your mouth is",
        number:"3B",
        question:"My Friend 'X'",
        answer:"Players describe a former or current friend of theirs."
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"1",
        question:"My wishes for the holiday are quite simple, There's only one essential desire in my heart, Unconcerned with the gifts beneath the Yuletide fir, My only yearning is to have you by my side, Beyond what you might ever imagine, Fulfill my holiday dream, You're the sole gift I yearn for this festive season.",
        answer:"All I want for Christmas is You"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"2",
        question:"Previous Yuletide, I bestowed my affection upon you, Yet, promptly thereafter, you passed it on, This time, to shield myself from sorrow, I'll present it to a person extraordinary.",
        answer:"Last Christmas"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"3",
        question:"Quiet evening, sacred twilight, Herders tremble at the view, Splendors cascade from distant skies, Celestial beings chant in joy, The Redeemer has arrived.",
        answer:"Silent Night"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"4",
        question:"The signs of the festive season are everywhere now, Playthings fill each shop's display, Yet the loveliest view to behold is the evergreen that shall adorn, The entrance of your abode.",
        answer:"It's Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas - Michael Bublé"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"5",
        question:"In this luminous moment, it's the perfect occasion, To sway through the evening's charm, The time of jingle bells is a marvelous period, To slide joyfully in a single-steed open carriage.",
        answer:"Jingle Bell Rock"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"6",
        question:"You should keep an eye open, Refrain from shedding tears, Avoid sulking, Here's the reason I say this.",
        answer:"Santa Claus Is Coming to Town"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"7",
        question:"Ponder on the merry times I've overlooked, Consider all the gentlemen I've bypassed for a peck, In the coming year, I might maintain my niceness, Should you fulfill my holiday wishlist.",
        answer:"Santa Baby"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"8",
        question:"Honestly, I mustn't linger, Darling, it's quite chilly out there, I need to depart, Darling, it's quite chilly out there, Our time together has been, Awaiting your arrival, Truly delightful, I'll clasp your hands, as cold as frost.",
        answer:"Baby it's Cold Outside"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"9",
        question:"Ah, the climate outdoors is quite intimidating, Yet the blaze indoors is utterly charming, Given that we're confined with nowhere to venture, Permit the snowflakes to descend, let them cascade!",
        answer:"Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow!"
    },
    {
        round:"I Can't afford another lawsuit",
        number:"10",
        question:"Beneath the mistletoe in the evening's glow, She was oblivious to my stealthy descent, Down the steps to catch a glimpse, She assumed I was nestled, In my chamber, deep in slumber.",
        answer:"I Saw Mommy Kissing Santa Claus"
    }
];
